I
have all this O
[Music] has it
happened
yes or no can you see
that A
[Music] I was
making today's video come to the
side
that it is not there it has happened
Hello hello
friends
if many of you were commenting saying
enter and made a video of the SSP
then you guys can see the car has arrived it has
happened do it
[Music]
a car has met with an accident and has
arrived at our place now you can see I will
tell you what all is damaged in it
and its total cost the video will be
made later but right now I will tell you
what all is damaged in it okay
first of all you guys look at this
mirror here the challenger free lever
on bareilly and this predicate car
and this candidate Akbar
roof both the top and bottom are damaged and there is
a voucher here the black one is completely
broken
that green mirror you will have to
open it and check whether it is damaged
its water sweet you will have to check a little bit
some tips in the means now it may be
broken but it
looks good from outside so still check  It will be
and after that you should do a little bit,
this front panel with the rate
increases the entire self-confidence, look here, this will have to be completely
changed, it is completely scratched and
this side panel below, it has 125 written on it,
which is a scratch, this will have to be changed
and there may be a
difference in it, the alignment of the brand new eleven will also have to be
checked and for other
things also, it seems that after opening this show
[music] will the
chassis be straight or
not, right now it does not seem that it will be
straight,
I am looking at the English, see how much has it turned
on the handle, see how much has it turned,
now this
Team Anna Factor of yours and
this Express will have to be changed a little, ah,
rental will also be your bank handle, that will have to be
changed and here it will ask you whether
its clip is broken or not, I do
n't know if the wheel is broken then
Abhishek Lipta Dawood will have to be changed and
this footrest of it and this silencer of
vehicles
A Square 620 will have to come and on top of that,
this rear
right side rear panel has to be cross to
visit  If you have to, how much do I have to pay right now,
but all those people had commented that by
saying that a sexy video has been made, then a
video will be made, if you want to follow the channel and have
not subscribed yet, then
subscribe so that you can get all the
development notifications whenever you want, and those who are
watching
now, if there are any other friends in your friend circle,
please set them Kaya
MP3
after a few days, that's all for today, Jai Hind.